http://www.crsi.org/index.cfm/privacy

SearchQuick LinksCRSI MembershipShop CRSICase StudiesServices FinderCRSI ExplorerCRSI ConceptNavigationHomemyCRSI Event RegistrationsReinforcing BasicsBackReinforcing BasicsReinforcing BasicsReinforcing SteelBackReinforcing SteelReinforcing SteelReinforcing SteelRebar PropertiesBar IdentificationHandling/StorageSplicing BarsCorrosion-Resistance BarsBar TagsMill Test ReportHistory of Reinforcing SteelFAQs About BarsReinforced ConcreteBackReinforced ConcreteReinforced ConcreteReinforced ConcretePlacing BarsField InspectionFormworkBuildingsBackBuildingsBuildingsBuildingsFloor SystemsPreliminary Design ToolsBackPreliminary Design ToolsReinforced Concrete ExplorerReinforced Concrete ConceptBridgesBackBridgesBridgesBridgesBridge TypesPavementReinforced Concrete TerminologyIndustry AcronymsConcrete BenefitsBackConcrete BenefitsConcrete BenefitsFlexible DesignDurabilityFinancial SavingsSustainabilitySound/Vibration ControlAestheticsEconomy of ConstructionIndustry InnovationResource MaterialsMarketsBackMarketsOfficeHealthcareMultifamily ResidentialOtherRebar U e-LearningCRSI MembershipBackCRSI MembershipJoin CRSIBackJoin CRSIJoin CRSIProfessional MembershipStudent MembershipMembers OnlyShop CRSIServices FinderCase StudiesBackCase StudiesSearchBuildingsBackBuildingsBuildingsCommercial/IndustrialOfficeHealthcarePublicK-12 SchoolsUniversity FacilitiesCorrectional FacilitiesSingle FamilyMultifamilySports StadiumsMuseumsParking StructuresTransportationBackTransportationTransportationBridgesPavementTransportation FacilitiesTunnelsAbout CRSIBackAbout CRSIThe InstituteTechnical ExpertiseStaff DirectoryRegional OfficesCRSI HONORSBackCRSI HONORSAbout HONORS2020 Award Winners2018 Award Winners2016 Award Winners2013 Award WinnersMedia CenterBackMedia CenterMedia CenterPress RoomCRSI Logo Files and GuidelinesCRSI YouTube ChannelCRSI Interest GroupsCRSI Education & Research FoundationIndustry AffiliatesCareer OpportunitiesCertification, Standards, EPDBackCertification, Standards, EPDCertification, Standards, EPDCertification/Standards/EPDEpoxy Coating Plant CertificationEpoxy Bar Fabricator CertificationStainless Steel Fabricator CertificationCRSI StandardsEnvironmental Product Declaration (EPD)Government Affairs (Public)Members OnlyBackMembers OnlyMembers OnlymyCRSI ProfilemyCRSI TransactionsUpcoming CRSI EventsCommittee Central (Member)Market Dashboard (Member)BackMarket Dashboard (Member)Market Dashboard (Member)Consumption Report ArchiveForecast Report ArchiveRegion Marketing PlansEPD Document (Member)Competitive ThreatsBackCompetitive ThreatsCompetitive ThreatsGFRPGovernment Affairs (Member)BackGovernment Affairs (Member)Government Affairs (Member)Gov't Affairs Landing PageAdvocacy and ActionContribute/RebarPACIndustry CoalitionsInfrastructure Legislation/InvestmentSurface Transportation 5-Year ReauthorizationResilient Construction/Code AdvocacyTall Wood BuildingsWater Resources Development Act (WRDA) ReauthorizationBuy AmericaSkilled Workforce ShortageSafety Corner (Member)BackSafety Corner (Member)Safety Corner (Member)Workplace Safety Files and DocsRadius Bending Safe Operating ProcedureBender Operator Safe Work ProcedureSchnell Automatic Pre-Flight ChecklistEVG
LOTO ProcedureAutomatic Coil Bender Safe Work ProcedureAlligator Shear Safe Operating ProcedureTrailer Fall Protection General Safety AwarenessHydraulic Shear
Safe Operating ProcedureSafety Posters & SignsJobsite Safety Files and DocsTool Box TalksRisk AssessmentsDetailer Training Program (Fabricator Member)Institute Publications (Member)Conference/Meeting Files (Member)Membership Directory (Member)Institute Logos/Guidelines (Member)Concord Purchasing Program (Members)Members in PhotosContactSitemap CRSI MembershipServices FinderShop CRSICase StudiesCRSI ExplorerCRSI Concept
Privacy Policy
Home
CONCRETE REINFORCING STEEL INSTITUTE PRIVACY POLICY
The Concrete Reinforcing Steel Institute has adopted this Privacy Policy (“Policy”) to govern the collection, use, and storage of data. (“CRSI,” “We” or “Us,” as used in this Policy, may include CRSI subsidiaries and affiliated entities.) CRSI, the authoritative resource for steel reinforced concrete construction information, places a high priority on protecting your privacy. This Policy was created in order to demonstrate the CRSI’s commitment to the privacy of our members and website users. This policy explains what types of information is collected by the CRSI and how this information is used. This Policy governs all forms of Personal Data collected by CRSI whether electronic, written or oral. By accessing our website or providing your information to us, you accept and agree to the practices described in this Policy.
What Types of Data We Collect
We collect a variety of information when you visit our website(s) and engage with our services. CRSI members that register on www.crsi.org and individuals that sign up to receive CRSI e-communications voluntarily provide us with contact information.
Personal Data may include your name, phone, email, physical and/or billing address, and credit card information, either personal or work (or both), and may include demographics such as occupation or job title, and identifies you as an individual or is information that can be linked to you as an individual (“Personal Data”).
Internet Protocol (IP) Addresses
CRSI uses your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer www.crsi.org, and for statistical metrics used to track website visitor traffic.
How We Collect Personal Data
In general, a visitor will know when Personal Data is being collected because he or she may have to complete a contact form, fill out a survey or evaluation, and/or create an account. In addition, we may collect Personal Data through your use of the website(s), e-learning portal (Rebar U), or Apps. Visitors may generally browse public portions of the CRSI website(s) anonymously without providing any detailed information. However, Personal Data is required in connection with registering within the site for purchasing or registering for membership, event activities, products or services, requesting additional information, signing up for newsletters, or submitting questions through this site. CRSI does not knowingly collect or use any Personal Data from users under 13 years of age.
How We May Use Your Personal Data
We use your Personal Data to provide you with personalized service: to send e-mail alerts and newsletters to you; to provide you with product or event updates; to answer your requests; to process your membership application; to process your meeting registration; to complete an order you place for merchandise through CRSI's online store, to register you for an e-learning course or webinar; etc. We may use the information you provide to inform you of other CRSI news, product, event or service offerings. We may also use your information to track visits to our website. This lets us see which of our features are the most popular so we can better serve our users’ needs. It also lets us provide aggregate data about our traffic (not identifying you personally, but showing how many visitors used which features, for example) to outside parties.
Cookies
A "cookie" is a piece of data stored on your hard drive containing information about you. CRSI may use cookies in order to collect certain information about you, such as IP addresses (the Internet address of a computer), domain names (e.g., whether you are logged on from a .com, .gov, or .edu domain) and the type of computer and operating system being used. We may also use cookies to identify your computer when you revisit our website or to recall your authentication information. CRSI uses application program interfaces (API’s) to create transitions from our public website, e-commerce store, e-learning portal, members only section, etc. by minimizing the number of times you have to log in. These API’s may use session cookies and/or web tokens in order to function properly. CRSI may collect such information in order to better operate the website so as to enhance your experience while using the website. You have the option of setting your computer to disable cookies or to alert you when cookies are being used. If you choose to disable cookies, please be aware that portions of the Site may not function properly.
How We Share Information
CRSI may provide personal information to third party agents that have been hired to help provide a requested good or service such as payment processors, website analytics services, etc. CRSI does not share or sell data to third parties for marketing purposes. Visitors may opt-out from the sharing of collected information by contacting the Data Controller at gdpr@crsi.org or by calling 1-847-517-1200.
CRSI reserves the right to disclose without notice any information in its possession if required to do so by law, to protect or defend CRSI’s rights or property, or to respond to an emergency.
External Links
This Policy only addresses CRSI’s use and disclosure of your Personal Data. The CRSI website(s) and Apps may contain links to other websites, so please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites, and we are not liable for their misuse of Personal Data. We encourage you to be aware that when you go to another website you should carefully read their privacy policy. Links to other sites do not imply CRSI’s endorsement of the products or services, or privacy or security practices of those websites.
Our Security Protections
CRSI does its utmost to prevent unauthorized access and safeguard member data, and to ensure data accuracy for correct online usage. CRSI has taken maximum precaution to guard the safety of online financial transactions. Credit card data is encrypted and securely transmitted. If you prefer not to use a credit card for online transactions, please contact CRSI directly at 1-847-517-1200 or email crsi@crsi.org.
We use commercially reasonable efforts to make our collection of data consistent with all applicable laws and regulations. We restrict access to Personal Data to our employees, contractors and service who need to know the information to operate, develop, or improve our services. We exercise care in providing secure transmission and storage of data. However, no data transmission or storage is 100% secure. We cannot warrant that all data we transmit, store and collect will be completely secure. We take commercially reasonable efforts to create and maintain firewalls, restricted access and other appropriate safeguards to ensure that, to the extent we control information, it is used only as authorized by us and consistently with this Policy.
We retain your Personal Data for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services, comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements.
Your Privacy Options
We respect your privacy and recognize your right to limit how we contact you and share information. We will endeavor to correct, update or remove collected Personal Data if contacted. When we contact you by email, all broadcast email campaigns from CRSI will contain instructions and/or hyper-links to Opt In or Opt Out (unsubscribe) of our email lists. Occasionally, especially with member correspondence, an email may originate from a CRSI employee’s company email account that will not contain an opt-out option. In addition, e-mail addresses may be removed from CRSI e-mail lists at any time by contacting CRSI as outlined below.
CRSI acknowledges that you have the right to access your Personal Data. In case you request us to remove data, we will respond within a reasonable timeframe.
Upon request, CRSI will provide you with information about whether we hold any of your Personal Data. You can update or correct your Personal Data or remove it from our system by logging into your member profile or by making a request to us at the contact information provided below. Requests typically receive a response within thirty (30) days. If access cannot be provided within that time frame, we will provide the requesting party with an estimated date by which the information will be provided. If for some reason access is denied, we will provide an explanation of why access has been denied. If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible at the address below. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect.
Changes to the Privacy Policy
CRSI reserves the right to modify this Policy at any time without prior notice. Your continued use of this website shall constitute your acceptance of the Policy.
Contact Us
Questions or comments about this Privacy Policy should be directed to:
